- All right.
- Go away.
(Sheldon:)If you're concerned about sharing credit
with me, your name can go first... I'm going.
(Howard(into phone):)It's a small brown paper bag, Ma.
(Howard(into phone):)I'm looking at it right now.
Why would I make that up?
There's no Ding Dong in it.
How are two Ding Dongs tomorrow
gonna help me today?
(Sheldon(entering):)So this is Engineering, huh?
(Howard(into phone):)I'll talk to you later.
(Sheldon(entering):)Engineering,
where the noble semiskilled laborers...
(Sheldon:)...execute the vision
of those who think and dream.
Hello, Oompa Loompas of science.
(Howard:)Sheldon, what are you doing here?
(Sheldon:)I just came by to say hello.
(Howard:)For three years,
you've never come by to say hello.
(Sheldon:)Well, up until now,
I've had better things to do.